Yes?
Hello, Teshigawara-sensei?
It's Uchiyamada.
What's happened?
The special advanced class
is about to begin!
I'm sorry.
I'm not feeling too well...
Could you please let me
rest for a while?
For a while?
That presents us with a problem,
Teshigawara-sensei!
Without you, what will happen
to the special advanced class?
What are we going to do, sir?
They say when the elite
are set back,
it takes time for them to recover.
The special class is our creation.
If it fails, what will
the parents say!
I know already!
- Fuyutsuki-sensei.
- Yes?
For now, could you switch
English for the first hour?
But...
Could you hurry, and explain
to the students too.
I understand.
That takes care of the first hour,
but what will do about
Mathematics?
We can't cancel Mathematics.
There is no choice, I'll do it!
Will you be okay?
I must keep it going.
It's important to keep in contact
with the students.
It's important for face
to face contact.
Magnificent!
And in the future, when you
become principal,
you won't have the opportunity
to do that.
I'm not saying this
because of that!
I've felt that it was strange
to leave the principal's
post open.
The head teacher is expected
to become the next principal.
Just what is the director thinking!
Sir,
when that time comes,
you'll become the head teacher.
Oh no! I'm not...
Please, Principal.
Thank you, Head Teacher!
Onizuka! You again!
Wake up! What are you doing!
- Oh, good morning.
- Didn't we tell you!
Don't ever use this
as a hotel room!
I wasn't!
I'm the security guard,
so I have to make rounds.
That being the case,
I figured it best
to be in the most valuable spot,
the principal's office.
Onizuka-sensei!
- I got the watermelon!
- Thanks!
I thought we could eat
it together...
Fujitomi-sensei,
what are you doing here too!
Yes, well...
I invited him. I asked him
to come to school.
Excuse me, but there's nothing
for me to do at home.
No matter how much A/C
there's in this room,
it isn't a place for you
to relax and rest!
If you keep doing this,
I won't forgive you!
- Get out!
- What a grump.
Shaddap!
Oh, geeze!
Man it's hot!
This ain't fun either.
Oh, Onizuka-sensei! How about it,
why don't you join us?
I'll pass, I don't need
the exercise.
Come on! When it's hot,
it's best to sweat it out!
If you stay in where there's A/C,
you'll end up sick like
Teshigawara-sensei.
I know already!
You know, I've always thought
that something
was wrong with
Teshigawara-sensei,
with his obsession with
university admissions.
The most important thing
is that the student
and teachers share their feelings.
Don't you think that's the key?
Not that I'm boasting,
but I've never
resorted to corporal punishment.
If you appeal to their hearts,
then the students will
understand your feelings.
In reality, there are no bad kids.
That is how I truly feel.
Could it be...
Hakamada-sensei, did you idolize
Kinpachi-sensei
and decided to become
a teacher because of that?
- You can tell?
- Hey, I'm "Super"!
I've seen that about
a hundred times!
"I am not teaching rotten apples!"
"They're living human beings!"
I like Nakamura Masatoshi too.
"Tears are the sweat of the soul!"
- I know, Onizuka-sensei.
- Huh?
Your worried about your class,
2-4, aren't you?
Terrible, isn't it?
Saying they're boycotting class
until they get
- a different homeroom teacher.
- That's right! They're so brazen!
Alright then, I'll help you out!
What?
In any case, it's hot, so could you
stand at least a meter away?
I will convince everyone
to return to your class.
If you don't by fall,
you'll be fired, right?
Yeah, but I'm sure something'll
happen by then...
You know, I'm pretty popular
with the students.
I don't know how many
chocolates I got on Valentines!
- Hakamada-sensei...
- Leave it to me!
If I convince Murai Kunio
and Aizawa Miyabi,
then something will happen.
- They control the class.
- Yes, but I...
Don't worry about it!
Leave it to me!
I will find a solution!
Oh, geeze...
SORIMACHI TAKASHI
MATSUSHIMA NANAKO
KONDÔ YOSHIMASA
NUMATA BAKU
KOBAYASHI MASAHIRO
IDA KUNIHIKO
KIRARI
IKEUCHI HIROYUKI
KUBOZUKA YÔSUKE
NAKAMURA AIMI
YAMAZAKI YÛTA
TOKUYAMA HIDENORI
FUJIKI NAOHITO
MABUCHI ERIKA
TATEISHI RYÔKO
RIKAKO MURAKAMI
NAKAO AKIRA
English Subtitles by
STUDIO NEW MEDIA
Subtitles Edited and Timed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Directed by
NAKAJIMA SATORU
A Production of
KANSAI TEREBI & AVEC
Yo! Murai!
How about going for a run
with me?
What you need most now
is to sweat.
Sorry, but I've got the special
advanced class.
- I know, Murai.
- What's that?
Something's bothering you.
Don't hold back,
talk to me about it.
I ain't got anything to talk
to you about.
Alright then!
Let's have a contest!
Why should I do that?
If I win, then I want you
to promise to return
to Onizuka-sensei's class
in the fall.
Oh, I see.
So Onizuka-sensei
asked you to help.
I heard you were a star swimmer
in intermediate school.
Well, I'll teach you that outside,
there's always someone better.
1,000 yen on Hakamada!
- Me too!
- And me!
Hey you guys, that doesn't
make a bet! Geeze!
- 4,000 yen on Murai!
- What?
Onitchi! Shouldn't you bet
on Hakamada?
That's right! He's trying
to convince Murai.
Stupid! That and this
is a different thing!
How's that, Murai?
Such a workout makes you
forget all your troubles...
No... no way!
I was a little unprepared before.
And swimming is your
specialty too.
But that won't happen
in the 100 meters.
Sorry about this, Murai.
But don't feel bad if you lose.
I am a phys ed teacher, after all.
Okay!
How?!
1,000 yen!
Oh, thanks! Sorry!
Hey! Murai!
Good work!
Hey, thanks to you,
I made quite a bit!
I'll treat you to something.
- How low can you go?
- What's that?
You shouldn't go asking
Hakamada to try
and convince us for you.
That idiot just decided
on his own...
Stop making excuses.
If we don't return to class by fall,
you'll be fired.
That's right! I always forget
about that!
Yeah right! I'm sure you're
worried about it.
Not really. Whether I worry
or not, you won't come back
to school anyway, right?
Then are you just going
to ignore it?
So...
do you have any good ideas?
How can I get you to end
your boycott?
Why ask me?
Hey, Murai!
Because the best person to ask
about you, is you, right?
C'mon, I'll give you
the 8,000 yen I just won.
Damn! That was close!
Look where you're driving,
dumb ass!
What about you?
Why don't you look where
you're walking, dimwit!
Mom...
Kunio-kun, this is your mom?
Kunio, who the heck is this?
My homeroom teacher.
Homeroom teacher!
Pleased to meet you,
I'm Onizuka Eikichi.
I'm so sorry!
I thought for sure you were one
of those punks. I'm sorry!
But I was so surprised
that Murai-kun's mom
is so young and pretty!
Oh my, you're such
a sweet talker.
But being a truck driver
is pretty cool!
It's nothing but hard work,
there's a lot of all-nighters.
But the pay is good.
Because he doesn't
have a father,
I have to make sure everything
is provided for.
That's why Kunio worked so hard
to get into Seirin Academy.
You're great! You are
the epitomy of a mother!
How embarrassing!
Don't say that!
- Right, Kunio-kun?
- Whatcha looking at!
What are you talking about?
Don't play innocent,
you pervert teacher!
What are you saying, Kunio!
He was checking you
out just now!
He wouldn't do that!
He's your homeroom teacher.
Don't be stupid!
I'm sorry, I think he suffers from
a bit of a mother complex.
That's alright. I think all men
suffer from a mother complex.
It's times like this that
makes me think,
it'd be better if he had a father.
Oh? What happened
to his father?
Just after Kunio was born,
he was in a motorcycle accident.
He was so reckless!
Here.
This!
He's Murai-san,
the great third Wild Angel!
- Oh? You know him?
- Of course!
There isn't anyone in the Shônan
that doesn't know him!
Does that mean you were
formerly a gang member?
Yeah, well,
I wasn't anyone important.
Oh! No wonder it's so easy
for me to talk to you!
Isn't it?
Hey Murai! Your dad was
a great person, you know!
- He was like a god to us!
- I don't care!
You have to excuse him.
Whenever talk of his father
comes up,
he always get's like this.
That's why I've got more
cool pictures,
but this is the only one
we put up.
Kunio-kun's more delicate
than he looks, isn't he?
- You can tell?
- Yes, I can!
At that age, they go through
so many emotions
and things they don't
understand.
You're so right!
I'm so glad I was able to talk
to you, Onizuka-sensei!
Because you know, every time
I went in to discuss things,
his homeroom teacher
would be different.
Leave it to me!
You can come to me anytime!
Oh! I'm so glad!
What's with your big
teacher act!
Kunio! How dare you
talk like that!
Don't be fooled! This guy just
wants to do it with you!
Can't you see that!
Don't I always tell you, don't
judge people by their looks!
Come here!
I'm sorry.
He wasn't always like that.
He used to say, when he
grew up, he'd take care of me.
He said he was going
to become a lawyer.
With that kind of attitude,
nothing will change.
Fuyutsuki-sensei,
are you listening?
What? Of course!
You're talking about
Murai-kun, right?
He won't understand how
I feel at all.
Is he mistakenly applying
his boycott to me?
No, I don't think so.
Really? I think you're the only one
who'll say that, Fuyutsuki-sensei.
But I can't give up just
because of this.
Like Kinpachi-sensei, I was
worried about his suffering!
That's right! You can't give up!
I'm glad I had a chance to talk
to you, Fuyutsuki-sensei!
I've gotten the motivation back
to try again tomorrow!
Let's drink up tonight!
Oh! Look at the time!
I have to go...
You know, I have many dreams...
First, to have our track
and swimming teams
nationally ranked.
And then...
I've found my marriage partner
within the teaching department.
Such enthusiasm in teaching,
to work hand in hand,
isn't that the perfect teacher?
Fuyutsuki-sensei,
are you listening?
- What?
- Right?
Of course!
Um...
Fuyutsuki-sensei...
would you like to be with me
to make my dream...
Let's go somewhere else!
I can't relax here.
Of course! We should go
somewhere quieter
to discuss things this important.
Excuse me, check please!
Oh!
Onizuka-sensei?
Hey! Good to see you!
Oh? Could you be on a date?
What? What are you saying!
Hakamada-sensei and I would
never do something like that!
Hakamada-sensei just needed
to discuss some things,
so I'm here to listen.
So, are you on a date?
- No, we're not, right?
- Don't...
It's a parent teacher conference.
Don't try to fool me!
Such a young and beautiful
woman, she can't be a parent.
I'm sorry he's always
so much trouble.
I'm Murai Kunio's mother.
- What?
- There!
If you're 34...
then you had Kunio-kun
when you were 17?
Right. At that time,
I wholeheartedly was
determined to have him.
Oh, did we argue!
My parents were really harsh!
But right after he was born,
you lost your husband, right?
- Yup.
- Didn't you have any regrets?
Not at all! Because I gave birth
to the child of the man I loved
the most in the world!
So, Fuyutsuki-sensei, is there
someone you're in love with?
What?
- Oops!
- That's cold!
- Oh! I'm sorry!
- That tickles!
- There isn't anyone!
- So, what's your type?
It doesn't matter!
No, we want to know,
right Onizuka-sensei?
- What? Sure.
- I'm fine!
What have you been
doing here, Onizuka-sensei?
What? What do you mean?
Murai-san, you better
watch out for this man.
Why's that?
Even though he's a teacher,
there's no knowing what he'll do!
Oh no! He didn't do anything
strange to you already, did he?
Of course not!
Being with him is enjoyable!
Me too! I almost forget that we
are a parent and a teacher.
You see, Onizuka-sensei reminds
me of my late husband.
What! No! I'm nothing
compared to Murai-san!
If he doesn't have a girlfriend,
then I might fall for him!
That's my line!
Do you really not have
a boyfriend?
No, I don't!
Excuse me, but what we were
just talking about...
- Huh? What was that?
- About Fuyutsuki-sensei's type!
Oh! That's right!
I think her ideals might
be pretty high.
For example, his references
need to be perfect.
When I was young, I felt like that.
But now, I think it's "heart",
someone with enthusiasm,
like Hakamada-sensei!
No way!
And someone with big dreams,
like Hakamada-sensei!
Oh, Fuyutsuki-sensei!
Oh my! Could it be you two
are already an item?
What are you saying!
We're not like that at all!
You should see each other!
Since you're such
an ideal couple!
- It shouldn't concern you, right?
- Hakamada-sensei,
invite me to the wedding,
I'll go get a tuxedo!
Stop it, Onizuka-sensei!
Murai-san, please let me know
if he does something weird,
- I'll call the police.
- Hey now!
Would you please stop accusing
others of being perverts!
Well, will you stop assuming
things about people?
I'm just concerned for you!
Well, I'm not stupid enough
to need your concern!
What's with the way she's talking!
Do you think a man could
fall in love with that?
I'm not going to listen to such
a deficient man like you!
Oh yeah?
Who's the deficient one?
What? You're full of deficiencies!
What! Show me a deficiency,
show me!
- Your full of deficiencies!
- Like where?
Anata ni aitakute
Aitakute
Nemure nuyoru wa...
Onizuka-sensei, um...
Oh, what number do you want?
Oh no, I'm no good
at karaoke at all.
It's about Fuyutsuki-sensei.
What?
I should confess my love,
shouldn't I?
What?!
Would it be better if I proposed?
You should do whatever.
Then... you'll support me,
Onizuka-sensei?
Sure, sure.
Thank you! I'll do my best!
Thank you!
Kôkai shinai deshô
Kanashimi ni deau tabi
So...
Fuyutsuki-sensei...
I'll bet you've never really fallen
in love with anyone yet,
- have you?
- Why do you say that?
That's just the feeling I get.
So, what made you decide
to marry your late husband?
I wonder if it was the throbbing
in my heart.
- Throbbing?
- Yup, for example,
if I'm not with him,
it's totally boring.
I see...
So... is there anyone
like that in your life?
- Of course not!
- If you do,
just because you're a woman,
you better not wait to confess.
Because you know, that person
may be dead tomorrow.
Could it be...
that you were the one
who proposed, Tsubasa-san?
Of course!
If I didn't then,
then I think I would have
regretted it my whole life!
Because Kunio wasn't born yet.
So, what are you
going to do now?
Alright! Let's hit one more place!
I've got the special advanced
class tomorrow
and have to wake up early.
Sorry, I've got gym
tomorrow too.
Really? It's summer vacation
and you're working so hard!
What about you, Ei-chan?
I've got nothing to do,
so I'll stay with you.
Yay! I'm so happy!
Okay! Let's party it up tonight!
- Excuse us.
- Bye!
Good night!
Do you think, tonight,
those two might...
What?!
They wouldn't, right?
They're parent and teacher!
Of course!
- Oh! Good morning!
- What are you doing?
It's so stinking hot at my place,
I figured I'd go into
the principal's office.
- Don't tell Uchiyamada!
- Oh! Your clothes!
You didn't!
You didn't...
with Murai-kun's mother...
We made the rounds,
she wouldn't let me sleep!
And so that's why you're
coming home in the morning?!
Not so loud!
You're making my head ring!
Aren't you embarrassed at all?
Doing things like that with
a student's mother!
- Things like what?
- It's no use lying!
From the beginning, I thought
the way you were looking
- at her was inappropriate!
- I couldn't help it!
Unlike someone I know,
Murai's mother is quite sexy.
That's what I mean
by inappropriate!
Oh, I see! You're jealous!
What?! Why would I be!
If you were just sincere
and asked,
I would have told you
if something happened last night.
Well, I didn't want
to know anyway!
So, didn't something happen
with Hakamada and you?
Hakamada-sensei isn't such
a vulgar man like you!
Oh really? Then why don't you
go out with him,
or are you going to keep me?
Sorry to disappoint you,
I've stopped doing that.
- Why the change of heart?
- Because...
That's because...
I've woken up to education.
Unlike you who comes to
school to play,
I'm busy with the special
advanced class!
Good night.
I'm still talking to you...
What a pig!
Ouch!
For crying out loud!
Damn!
That Onizuka pisses me off!
There's no need to get so mad.
- Come fall, he'll be fired.
- I know, but...
What is it?
It's nothing.
I just remembered...
About him...
It's almost the anniversary
of his death.
Hey, Murai!
How about it, want to have
lunch together?
Sorry, but we're busy.
Don't be like that!
I want to talk to you!
Didn't you hear, we don't
have time for that.
Hey! Hold on! Wait!
They don't even try
to understand others' feelings!
- Oh, that feels great!
- How's that?
Not there, it tickles!
Stop it!
- Oh! Welcome home, Kunio!
- Yo Murai! Welcome home!
Wow! Check it out!
This is really Murai-san's!
- Can I have this?
- Sorry, not that.
Can I borrow it? It's so cool!
What's this?
Get out!
What's wrong, Kunio?
They're here because they really
liked your dad, you know!
That's right Murai! Do you know
how much we looked up to him?
He ain't my father to me!
Watch what you say!
Do you know why he died?
Some trash about
a man's challenge!
He died proving his courage
on a bike.
How can you look up to
a fool like that!
- Now, now...
- Why you!
Stop it!
He left his family.
How can I love a man who just
goes off and dies!
You were just bike gangs,
don't go working him up
into something!
What's that, you punk!
- Kunio, stop it!
- Come on!
Stop it! Please!
You know, Onizuka-sensei...
He's a good man.
Men nowadays are usually all
so pathetic, but he's different.
I think I could trust him,
don't you?
There's no way I could trust
a teacher!
Why are you like that now?
What happened?
Why don't you tell me already?
It was after your best
friend died...
I told you!
Never bring that up again!
UCHIYAMADA
X minus...
Why is high school math so hard...
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Mama, could you be a little
more quiet, I'm trying to study.
Oh? Why does the head teacher
have to do that?
It can't be helped,
Teshigawara from mathematics
suddenly took time off.
Oh?
Say, wasn't that the man he was
complimenting before?
- That's right!
- Listen, Yoshiko.
These elite from Tôdai,
when it comes to a critical
moment, they're useless.
- Don't get involved with them.
- There's no need to worry.
Eikichi's the only one for me.
Eikichi?
Is that the one who called
last time?
You think so highly of him,
I told you to invite him over.
Mama, are you checking out
young guys?
What are you talking about!
As your mother,
I'm just concerned!
- Oh, Mom.
- Yoshiko!
You should give up on
worthless men like him.
But, Eikichi is a teacher,
you know!
- Really?
- Yes.
- Where? What school?
- I don't know.
Why didn't you ask about that?
The name or title doesn't
matter to me.
What's important...
is love!
Eikichi... I'm going to call him!
A teacher?
Eikichi...
Thank you for seeing me all
the way home.
I thoroughly enjoyed today.
Promise, now, right?
You can count on me.
Tomorrow then?
I'm looking forward to it!
Oh! You're home!
Good morning!
Did you stay over
in the principal's office again?
Last night was too hot.
Don't tell Uchiyamada.
What is that?
Here, pheromone perfume,
want some?
- No, thank you!
- Okay...
Are you going out on date now?
You can tell?
Could it be, with Murai-kun's
mother again?!
You can tell?
Could it be...
You're really serious this time?
Just what are you thinking!
I'm off!
"Zetsurin Super"?
Murai-kun! I've been
waiting for you!
Don't you ever come close
to my mom!
Why? You can't dictate
her love life.
Don't you try too fool
a student's mother,
you pervert teacher!
You don't have any right poking
in an adult's relationship, kid.
- What the...!
- Okay, okay!
If it bugs you so much,
then let's have a match.
Fuyutsuki-sensei,
what are you doing?
Well...
- Hakamada-sensei.
- Yes?
Could you come with me?
- Sure!
- Thank you!
Mom?
The first to run loses.
I want to give you a taste
of what your father was doing.
Don't be stupid, you biker!
If you're scared, then you
can quit, Kunio-chan.
Go on home. Who's scared!
If I win,
then I'll do whatever you say.
- Then I want you to disappear.
- Sure, I got it.
I'm saying you'll have
to quit school!
I said I got it!
But on the other hand...
If I win, then I want you
to tell me everything.
- What are you talking about?
- About your best friend.
Your mom told me.
After some incident,
you started bullying your
homeroom teachers.
She talks too much...
So, how about it, Murai?
Alright.
- Sensei!
- What are you two doing?
Sensei! Don't be stupid!
Nuts, looks like some annoying
people've shown up.
Sensei! All set!
Ready!
Start!
Okay! Let's go!
- I... ain't gonna die!
- Stupid!
Stop it! You're really
going to die!
Why are you doing this!
Please! Stop it!
Hey! Stop!
What is this going to achieve?
Please! Stop!
Quit it! Stop!
- Hey! Is something wrong?
- That's getting too close!
- Onitchi!
- Hey?
Hey! Hey! What's going on?
Hey! Run!
Oh no! Hurry! Run!
You're really going to die!
- I... I can't!
- What?!
Mom!
She's okay.
Aren't you glad, Murai?
Ouch! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Tsubasa-san!
Are you okay?
I'm fine! I'm fine!
It'll take more than this
to kill me.
Kunio,
you lost, didn't you.
What do you mean!
I didn't run!
That's because you were
frozen with fear!
So...
hurry up and tell him.
- You see...
- Murai,
promise me one thing.
Huh?
Never talk bad about your
father again.
You see your dad,
loved your mother
with all his life.
He decided to love only her
for his whole life.
If you don't come to love him,
then your mother will
be sad, right?
See ya...
Onizuka-sensei!
Aren't you going to ask
about his secret?
This guy? He'll tell me
when he's ready.
Murai...
I'll always be waiting.
Okay?
Onizuka-sensei!
I thought Onizuka-sensei could
do something for you.
So I asked him.
But then the brakes failed!
I was supposed to stop
at the last second.
To have someone who would
risk his own life for you
as your homeroom teacher
is amazing!
You know, if I had someone like
him for my homeroom teacher,
I would have gone to school.
Stupid!
What did you want to talk about?
- You said before...
- What's that?
You said, he wasn't a teacher.
Yeah.
So you mean he's different
from other adults?
That he's different from all
the other instructor's we've had?
Yeah.
You... Are you going to...
talk to Onizuka about him?
What do you think?
What about Miyabi?
She'll never forgive you.
Yo, Murai! What's up?
I have something to talk
to Onizuka-sensei about.
If you've got something
to talk about, I'll listen.
Okay, what is it?
Murai, it's okay, you can tell me.
- Shaddap.
- C'mon, you can trust me!
You just want people
to believe you're a good person.
- What's that?
- You just preach to us.
You just want to see us
agree with you.
You don't really understand
any of our feelings!
You aren't really worried
or concerned for us!
Murai! Hey you!
Come back here!
What's with that attitude!
Don't mess with me!
Don't try to make a fool of me!
What are you looking at?
- Damn you!
- C'mon!
Who do you think you are?
Murai, you're just a spoiled brat!
- What are you doing!
- Do you hear me?
Stop it!
I'm talking to you!
Do you hear me?!
That Onizuka, he's no teacher!
He's nothing!
Hakamada-sensei!
Why won't you talk to me!
You hear me?
Please stop!
This'll be corporal punishment!
Murai-kun.
This is why I can't trust teachers!
Murai-kun!
- You've been mistaken.
- Fuyutsuki-sensei...
Certainly, it may be wonderful
to sweat.
However... as a teacher...
you should first think
of the students.
Don't you think that's
more important?
Don't ever betray me again!
Ready!
I ain't gonna die!
- I'm Murai, 'k!
- Okay!
Oh no! My foot's stuck
and I can't move!
Your arms are all wrong.
You're holding your
arms all wrong!
Like this, 45 degrees.
2016-05